本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
这款T恤有我穿的型号吗
Do you have this T-shirt in my size?
我有更好的东西
I have something even better.
瞧  我的屁股
Behold! My butt!
我可以一辈子像这样玩下去
I could play this game forever.
-你说什么  -咳嗽  我在咳嗽
- What'd you say?  - Coughing! I was coughing!
-什么话都没说  -哈哈
- Those weren't words!  - Ha ha ha ha!
真有趣  你们两个
This if fun, what you two have.
梅宝  你在那里站了多久了
Mabel! How long have you been standing there?
别担心
Don't worry about that.
不如聊聊为什么我在跳这个舞吧
Let's talk about why I'm doing this dance!
不  她又吃笑笑糖了
Oh no! She got into the smile dip again!
大错特错
Wrong one thousand!
因为今天是我人生中最重要的日子
It's because today is the greatest day of my life!
多次乐队将要在
Sev'ral Timez is playing
重力泉城市中心演出
at the Gravity Falls Civic Center and buffet!
啊  多次乐队
Ahh. Sev'ral timez?
他们不是那个应该十年前出道的男孩乐队吗
Aren't they that boy band that came a decade too late?
姑娘  你让我行为如此疯狂
Girl, you got me actin' so cray cray
-疯狂  -你说你不会做我的宝贝
- Cray cray!  - You tell me that you won't be my baby
我们并不危险
We're not threatening!
梅宝  你知道所有的男孩乐队都是假的  对吗
Mabel, you know all those boy bands are fake, right?
迪普说得对  他们只是膨胀的音乐产业
Dipper's right. They're just a manufactured product
生产出的工业产品
Of the bloated corporate music industry.
你们让我的舞步很伤感
You're making my dance sad!
可能有一台机器批量制造了他们
There's probably a machine that mass produces them.
或者也可能他们是从培养舱里长出来的
Or maybe the boys are grown from pods.
对  培养舱  绝对是这样
Yeah! Pods, totally!
你们不能这么毁了我的偶像
You guys can't ruin this for me.
梅宝是有后援的
Mabel's got backup!
-你们好  -呜呼
- Hey, guys! - Whoo whoo!
我为我们人生中最重要的一天做好了准备
I'm ready for the greatest night of our lives!
我会爱你多少次
How many times am I gonna lova ya?
多次乐队
Sev'ral Timez!
-小姑娘们啊  -我知道  对吧
- Uhh. Girls.  - I know, right?
我没事
I'm okay.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
CC录制： ufohaman  Qin Cong
时间轴： WaitinZ
■
翻译： 溪傲季  Chamania
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第一季第十七集
Gravity Falls  S01E17  Boyz Crazy
我应该用润唇膏  还是防唇裂油膏
Ooh. Should I got with lip balm or lip salve?
狂野一点  今晚是我们的大日子
Go wild! Tonight's our night!
我迫不及待了  伙计们  今晚我们将要遇见
I can't wait, guys. Tonight we're gonna meet
克雷格・吉  克雷格・西
Creggy G, Greggy C,
莱格・皮  查比・齐和深度・克里斯
Leggy P, Chubby Z, and Deep Chris!
他是那个胖子
He's the fat one.
那些男孩们会爱上我们的
And those boys will fall in love with us.
为什么不呢
Why wouldn't they?
这里是无指手套店吗
Hey, this is the fingerless glove store?
我喜欢傻了吧唧的东西  我是罗比
I like things that are dumb. I'm Robbie.
拜托  伙计
Come on, man!
哈哈哈哈  尽管笑吧  主管
Ha ha ha ha ha. Laugh it up, chief.
温蒂  内特和他的
So, Wendy, Nate and his
女朋友这星期要去t望点
girlfriend are going to lookout point this weekend.
-也许我们也应该去  -你在耍我吗
- Maybe we should go, too. - Are you kidding me?!
首先昨晚你放了我的鸽子
First you stand me up last night,
然后你不仅不道歉
And instead of apologizing,
反而想要我去t望点
you want me to go to lookout point?
我还是  回避一下
I'll just be...over here.
听着  罗比  我想我们的感情出问题了
Look, Robbie. I'm not sure this relationship's working.
也许我该和别人约会试试
Maybe I should see other people.
好呀
Yes!
等等  在你做什么傻事之前
Whoa. Whoa. Hey. Hey. Before you do anything crazy,
我  我想让你听听这个
I, uh, I want you to hear this.
希望能管用
Hope this works.
我为你写了这首歌
I wrote this song just for you.
当我思念你
When I think about you
我感到了深深的情意
I feel feelings so deep
我辗转反侧
I'm tossin' and turnin'
你知道我无法入睡
And you know I'm losing sleep
-恶心  -我知道当我看着你的双眼
- Yeesh! - And I know I'm goin' crazy
我就会疯掉
when I look into your eyes
听这首歌
Jus listen to this song
你会被我催眠
And you'll be hypnoti-yi-yized
也许我刚才有点草率
You know, maybe I was being a little hasty.
我会再给你一次机会
I'll give you another chance.
太好了
Yes! All right!
我去拿外套
Let me go grab my coat.
喂  罗比  我看到那张古怪的唱片了
All right, Robbie, I saw that weird cd.
你准备干什么鬼事
What the heck are you up to?
这叫浪漫  小子  你永远也不会懂的东西
It's called romance, kid. Something you'd never understand.
准备好了吗
You ready?
不敢相信你为我写了那首歌
I can't believe you wrote that for me.
我理解  我就是这么天赋异禀
I know. I'm just so insanely talented.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
伙计们  刚才发生了一件最诡异的事
Guys, the weirdest thing just happened.
我觉得罗比用音乐把温蒂给催眠了
I think Robbie might be hypnotizing wendy with his music.
迪普  女孩子们喜欢音乐家
Oh, Dipper! Girls just like musicians.
-等你长大点会明白的  -我们一样大
- You'll understand when you're older. - We're the same age!
女孩比男孩成熟的早  对吗  格兰达
Girls mature faster than guys. Right, Grenda?
这是属于格兰达的时刻
Mmm... this is Grenda time!
好吧  姑娘们  你们都练习过
Okay, girls, have you all practiced
痴迷于男孩乐队的尖叫了吗
your obsessed boy band scream?
忽略他就行
Just gonna ignore that.
买票
Tickets, please!
你们来晚了  票已经卖完了
Too late, girls! The show is sold out.
今晚毁掉了
This night is ruined!
欢迎你  死神
I welcome you, death.
不  我说过我们要
No! I said we're going to
在今晚见多次乐队  我就一定要见到
meet Sev'ral Timez tonight, and I meant it!
我不会被区区一个“禁止入内”的标志给拦在外面
And I'm not gonna let a "Keep out" Sign keep us out!
后台入口  非工作人员禁止入内
为世界末日积存肉类食品
Stockin' meat for the apocalypse, doodla-doo.
我们都会死
We're all gonna die--
孩子  为何要踱步
What's with the pacing, kid?
你比平常看起来更反常了
You look even more freaked out than usual.
我也不知道  你不会明白的
Ah, I don't know. You wouldn't understand.
来吧  孩子  告诉我
Ah, come on, kid. Try me.
好吧  这听起来很奇怪
Okay. This is gonna sound weird,
我认为罗比可能用音乐把温蒂给洗脑了
But I think Robbie might be brainwashing Wendy with music.
这我曾经见过
I've seen this before.
-真的吗  -她叫卡拉・麦科克尔
- Really? - Her name was Carla McCorkle.
卡拉・“超短裤”・麦科克尔
Carla "Hot Pants" McCorkle...
我和她在小酒吧一起跳摇摆舞
Me and carla baby would cut a rug together at the juke joint,
是我们最爱的五十年代主题的七十年代餐馆
our favorite '50s-themed 1970s diner.
有一天  一个新潮的嬉皮士
Then one day, this new age tree-hugger
开始播放某种超凡的嬉皮音乐
Starts playing this transcendental hippie music.
我还没来得及反应过来
Carla's hot pants turned into bell-bottoms
卡拉的超短裤就变成了喇叭裤
Before I even knew what happened.
最后一部分记忆加入了一点幻想
My memories get a little hallucination-y at the end,
但是你领悟了主旨
But you get the gist.
等等  你竟然相信我的假设
So, wait. You actually believe my theory?
太相信了
You're darn right I do,
而且我们要弄清真相
and we're gonna get to the bottom of it.
让我先吃完这罐煎肉
Right after I get to the bottom of this brown meat.
末日的味道
It's apoca-licious!
多次乐队
Sev'ral Timez.
姑娘  我只是想在这一刻说点实在的话
Hey, girl, I just want to get real for a moment
我想说的是  虽然我们喜欢做大明星
And say that while we love being superstars,
但这么做的真正原因是为了你  只为你
The real reason we do this is for you, for you specifically,
不是站在你旁边的女孩  而是你
Not the girl sitting next to you, but you.
我爱你  深度・克里斯
I love you, Deep Chris!
他是对我说的
He was talking to me!
打得好  打得好
Git 'em! Git 'em!
感谢你们  晚安
Thank you! Good night!
有人在吗  多次乐队
Hello? Sev'ral Timez?
我们想给你们几个吻
We want to give you several kisses!
快看
Look!
就是这间
This is it, girls.
你们终于要遇见
You're finally going to meet
世界上最可爱的五个小伙子了
the five cutest boys in the world!
迪普说男孩乐队都是假的  他要食言了
Dipper's gonna eat his words that boy bands are fake.
真有趣
This is fun!
我们是克隆人  伙计
Yo! We're clones, dawg!
我的天
O... M... G!
这真是一个巨大的仓鼠笼
That is one big hamster tube.
有人来了
Someone's coming!
演出糟糕透了
Terrible show!
你们到底怎么了
What is wrong with you boys?!
差点连门票都没卖完
You barely even sold out the arena!
还有深度・克里斯  你的嘴撅得一点也不性感
And Deep Chris, you call that a pout?
你们都该为自己感到惭愧
Every one of you should be ashamed of yourselves!
除了你  莱格・皮  你今晚很到位
Except for you, Leggy P, you were really on point tonight.
吃吧  好孩子
Here ya go, gorgeous.
至于你们其他人  记好了
As for the rest of you, remember:
你们随时都能被自己的兄弟给替换掉
You can always be replaced by your brothers.
为我而跳舞吧  孩子  跳舞
Dance for me, child, dance!!!
我的嗓子真难受
My throat is killin' me!
谁能给我一杯柠檬水
Can someone get me a lemon and water?
谁在那里
Who goes there?
准备接受舞蹈吧
Prepared to be danced at!
退后  深度・克里斯
Step off, deep chris!
她是个女士  别失礼了  兄弟
She's a lady. Don't disrespect her, bro!
-别失礼  -我的错
- Don't disrespect! - Mah bad.
查比・齐  让我们用造型来使她冷静吧
Chubby Z, let's calm this boo by posin' for her,
造型模式
poster-style!
尽力让自己的脑袋别爆炸
Whoo! Trying hard not to let my brain explode!
我早就想见你们了
I've always wanted to meet you guys!
但是那个恐怖的胖男人是怎么回事
But what was the deal with that scary chub-chub man?
布拉茨曼先生是我们的制作人
Mr. Bratzman's our producer, yo.
他用基因工程把我们设计成了最完美的男孩乐队
He genetically engineered us to be the perfect boy band, g!
但是他把我们关在笼子里
But he keeps us in cages!
那个废物真是太残忍了  姑娘
That junk is straight brutal, girl!
的确很残忍  查比・齐
That is straight brutal, Chubby Z!
我们的梦想之一就是逃到真正的世界去  真的
Our one dream is to escape into the real world, for real.
我听说过一些叫树的东西
Yo, I heard tell about these things called trees?
虽然我不知道它们是什么  但很想找一个吻一吻
I don't know what they are, but I want to kiss one!
但是我们不能不服从布拉茨曼先生
But we can't disobey Mr. Bratzman!
他说他爱我们
He says he loves us!
如果他爱你们  他就该放你们走
If he loved you, he'd set you free!
不错
True dat.
是个合理意见
That's a valid perspective!
我们现在就走吧
Let's go right now.
我和我的朋友能帮你们逃跑
Me and my friends can help you escape.
我们是秘密行动大师
We're masters of stealth!
你真的要这样帮我们  牛肉
Yo! You'd really do that for us, beef?
你能指望我
You can count on me!
抱歉  你刚称呼我“牛肉”是吗
I'm sorry, did you just call me "Beef"?
瞧  迪普
You see, Dipper,
音乐总是隐藏着控制潜意识的能力
music has subliminal mind control hidden in it all the time.
如果你细心聆听  就连我
If you listen closely, even the music I play
在礼物店播放的音乐都有微妙的隐藏信息
in the gift shop has subtle hidden messages.
再买些钥匙扣
Buy more keychains!
如果你想听到控制意识的信息
If you want to hear the mind-controlling messages,
你需要慢放这张唱片
You gotta slow down the record.
把那张唱片给我
Gimme that L.P.!
好吧
Oh. Right.
我们肯定是哪里出了问题
We're doing something wrong here,
但我弄不清到底是啥不对劲
But I can't put my finger on it.
伙计们  演唱会怎样  包里面装的什么
Hey, guys! How was the concert? And what's in the bag?
钱  我们偷的钱
Uh, money. Money we stole.
我们是罪犯  我们会宰了你
We are criminals. We will cut you!
我们现在就走吧
Let's go away from here now!
轻点  姑娘
Dang, girl!
你们的旅行车真稀奇  梅宝姑娘
Your tour bus is really strange, Mabel girl.
喂食管道在哪里
Where the feeding tubes at?
你好啊  姑娘
Yo, what up, girl?
我们什么时候能去外面
So when do we get to go outside?
我想像林中生物一样跳跃
I want to cavort like a woodland creature!
是你们的制作人
It's your producer!
不敢相信那些男孩从笼子里逃走了
Can't believe those boys escaped from their cage!
站住  我发现这些头发丝
You there! I found this trail of frosted tips
将我引导了这个地方
leading to this very location!
你在这附近有没有看见几个完美的帅小伙
Have you seen any perfect boys around here?
只有在我照镜子的时候
Only when I look in the mirror.
哈哈  击个掌
Ha ha! Up top!
他们肯定就在这附近
They must be around here somewhere.
即使我把这个镇子翻个底朝天也要找到他们
I'll find those boys if I have to turn this town upside-down!
嘘  走开
Shoo! Shoo!
乖孩子
Good boy.
伙伴们  外面不安全
Guys, it's not safe out there.
尔格曼依然在寻找你们
Ergman's still looking for you!
我们怎么办
What do we do?
-该死  -我好怕  梅宝
- Oh, dang! - I'm scared, Mabel!
别担心  他最终会放弃的
Don't worry, guys, he has to give up eventually.
与此同时  你们能和我们呆在一起
Hey, in the meantime, you can stay here with us!
2013!
姐妹们  你们明白发生什么了吗
Girls, do you realize what's happening here?
我们有自己的宠物男孩乐队了
We have our very own pet boy band
我们能为所欲为了
that we can do whatever we want with!
别忘了  我们终归还是要放他们走
Remember, eventually we have to let them go.
所以我们最好不要对他们产生太深的感情
We have to promise not to get too attached to them.
你说是吧  梅宝  梅宝
Right, mabel? Mabel?
编小辫列车发车了
All aboard the braid train!
辫子  辫子
Braid, braid!
怎么了
What?
来吧  宝贝  和我一起翱翔吧
Come on, baby, won't you fly away with me?
拉住我的手  这是命中注定
Take my hand, it's destiny
我们不需要任何人  只要我们在一起
We don't need nobody if we stay together
女孩  抓住我的手  我们永远在一起
Girl, just take my hand, it can be forever
飞向天际  女孩  我们要飞了
Up into the sky, girl, we're gonna fly
看着我瞪大蓝色的眼睛
Look into my big blue eyes
女孩啊  你知道这是命中注定
Girl, you know it's destiny
拉住我的手  你将会看到
Take my hand and you're gonna see
让我们离开这儿  不理会世俗
Let's escape, running from reality
这样就永永远远在一起
It'll be this way forever
-慢着  再给我几分钟就行  -但是
Just a-- just a few more minutes. But--
好了
All right.
花了一天  终于把它转录成了唱片
Took all day, but I converted it to a record.
那我们现在就可以放慢速度  来看看
Now we can slow it down to see
思想控制的理论是不是正确的
if the mind control message theory is correct.
准备大吃一惊吧
Prepare to have your mind blown.
喝一口  我来也
Spit take, here I come.
当我思念你时
When I think about you
我感到
I feel
-我辗转反侧  -呃
- I'm tossing and turning - Hmm.
一点也不震撼啊  怎么回事
That's now spit-worthy. What gives?
什么  只有这样吗
What? Is that it?
哦  这真是太傻了
Ohh! This was so stupid!
世上当然没有什么控制意识的隐藏信息
Of course there's no hidden mind control messages!
梅宝是对的  温蒂仅仅是喜欢这首歌
Mabel was right. Wendy just likes the song.
-她就是喜欢罗比  -嗨  迪普
- She just likes Robbie. - Hey, Dip.
忘拿钥匙了
Forgot my keys.
怎么着啊  小孩  你在干嘛呢
What's up, junior? What are you doing,
绞尽脑汁想出一个
Trying to come up with an equation
让女孩子喜欢你的办法  哈哈哈
to make girls like you? Ha ha ha!
准备好去t望点了吗
Ready to go to lookout point?
还用说吗  回头见  蠢蛋
Am I. Later, dorks.
倒完带再见了
Catch you on the rewind.
（注：原俚语为Catch you on the flipside. 待会儿见）
这句是我编的
I made that up.
倒带你个头啊
I'll rewind your face!
等等  斯坦  倒带啊
Wait a minute. Stan, rewind!
你现在在我的掌控之下
You are now under my control
你的思想是我的
Your mind is mine
我的老天爷  这才有意思啊
Holy mackerel! Now there's your spit take!
哈哈  我就知道  果然还是有思想控制
Ha ha! I knew it! It's mind control after all.
哦不  我要去救温蒂
Oh, no! I gotta save Wendy!
终于找到痛扁年轻人的好理由了  咱们走吧
Finally, a good reason to punch a teenager in the face! Let's roll!
上面怎么样啊
How'd it go up there?
我终于让他们都睡下去了
Ohh. I finally got them to sleep.
可怜的克雷格・西  他想把胶带座吃下去呢
Poor Greggy C. He tried to eat a tape dispenser.
我觉得这个是食物  老兄
I think this is food, dawg!
你要一起分享吗
Yo, you gonna share that?
美好的回忆啊
Ah, memories.
音乐界传出了令人震惊的消息
The music industry was shaken today
男孩天团的经纪人尔格曼・布拉茨曼被逮捕
at the news that boy band king Ergman Bratzman has been arrested.
他今晚被警方拦下
He was pulled over tonight
因为没有挂后车牌
for not having a rear license plate.
我说了  山羊叼走了
I'm telling ya, the goat took it!
人们都是这么说
That's what they all say.
他现在在县监牢里等待审判
He is now in county jail awaiting trial.
-太好了  -我们得告诉男孩们他们现在自由了
- Yes! - We have to tell the boys they are free now!
快走
Let's go!
别这么快
Not so fast!
他们哪儿也不去
They're not going anywhere.
这是怎么了  梅宝
What the dealio, Mabel?
邪恶的制作人不在了  我们得告诉他们
That evil producer is gone. We have to tell the boys!
等等  姐妹们  别这么急  我的意思是
Wait, girls, let's not be so hasty. I mean,
想想吧  如果我们不告诉男孩们
Think about it: if we don't tell the boys,
那么他们就可以和我待在一起
Then they can stay here with me.
我是说我们
I mean with us.
梅宝  我们不能永远让他们留在这儿
Mabel, we can't keep them here forever.
但我真的很喜欢他们
But I love them!
如果你爱他们  你就该给他们自由
If you love them, you'd set them free.
绝不  这个夏天每一个我爱过的男孩都离我而去了
Never! Every boy I loved this summer has left me,
我绝对不会让这样的事再次发生
And I'm not gonna let it happen again!
糖糖  我们得解决梅宝  她得了迷恋男生花痴症
Candy, we gotta get past mable! She's gone boy-crazy!
男孩们
Uhh! Boys!!!
糖糖  进攻
Candy...attack!
哇  见鬼
Whoa! Dang!
男孩们  尔格曼・布拉茨曼进监狱了
You guys! Ergman Bratzman is in jail!
-你们自由了  -快走吧
- You're free! - Just go!
哦  那是真的吗  梅宝姑娘
Whoa! Is that true, Mabel dawg?
哦不  你们的制片人仍旧逍遥在外呢
Uh, no. Your producer's still out there.
你们还得呆在这儿  可能一辈子吧
You're gonna have to stay here-- probably forever!
什么  你们不能听她的
What?! You can't listen to her!
梅宝是我们的好姑娘
Mabel's our girl, girl.
她把披萨放在我们的食物槽里
She puts pizza in our food trough.
她更换我的报纸  她可好了
She changes my newspaper, yo. She's a'ight.
她一点也不好  查比・齐
She is not a'ight, Chubby Z!
多次乐队
Sev'ral Timez!
是  梅宝姑娘
Yes, Mabel dawg?
把这俩人弄出这栋房子  拜托了
Remove these two from the premises, please.
哦不  他们正在进攻性地向我们跳舞
Oh, no! They're aggressively dancing at us!
梅宝被权力冲昏头脑了
Mabel's gone mad with power!
醒醒吧  多次乐队
Save yourselves, Sev'ral Timez!
你们跟着那个制片人都比这样好
You were better off with your producer!
搞定
Word!
打电话给我  深度・克里斯
Call me, Deep Chris!
2013!
谢啦  伙计们
Thanks, you boys.
那我们现在来玩编小辫火车吧
Now let's get aboard the braid train.
事情变得有点棘手了  梅宝
Things just got pretty heavy, mabel.
或许我们应该冷静一下  再
Maybe we should all just like chill for a minute, and--
我说  快排成编小辫火车
I said, let's get aboard the braid train!!!
我们得警告温蒂那首歌  不然她会被洗脑的
We gotta warn Wendy about that song before she gets brainwashed!
道路安全法  准备好被无视吧
Road safety laws, prepare to be ignored!
呃  真奇怪  内特没有出现
Huh. Weird. Nate didn't show up.
所以我想应该就你和我了吧
So I-I guess it's just you and me.
这完全不在我的计划之内啊
This isn't what I was planning at all.
温蒂  等等  罗比骗了你
Wendy! Stop! Robbie's been lying to you!
-迪普  -小屁孩  派恩斯先生
- Dipper? - Kid? Mr. Pines?
应该是派恩斯先生
That's Mr. Pines to you!
什么  我不就是这么说的吗
What? That's what I just said.
你看  温蒂  你得听听这个
Look, Wendy. You've gotta hear this.
梅宝  你得听听这个
Mabel, you've gotta hear this.
这是我们写来感谢你的歌
It's a song we wrote to say thank you.
来吧
Hit it!
哦  天啊  歌曲就像嘴巴给耳朵的拥抱
Oh boy! Songs are like hugs that mouths give to ears!
这就是我们小小的梅宝姑娘
Here comes young Mabel girl
我们梦想自由
We've dreamed of bein' free
但我们却知这无法实现
But now we know that can never be
你知道什么是真正的朋友
You know what friends are all about
把这些谎话连篇的小矮子赶出去
You kicked those lyin' shorties out
都赶出去
Kick 'em out, y'all
我有点愧疚了啊
I'm starting to feel guilty here.
跳起来
Break it down!
是哪个女孩这么棒
Who's the girl who's so a'ight
每晚把我们裹进床里
Tucks us into bed at night
在我们唱歌时举着风扇
Holds the fan up while we sing
用绳子一直逗我开心
Keeps me entertained with string
我的衬衫皱了  多亏她帮我熨了
My shirt was wrinkled till she pressed it
嚼碎食物  我们就能消化了
Chews out food so we can digest it
他很邪恶  卑鄙又鲁莽
He was evil, mean and reckless
你却送我糖做的项链
You gave me this candied necklace
怎么了  姑娘
What's up, girl?
世事难料人心险恶
Other folks we could never trust
但我们知道
But we know
你永远不会骗我们的
That you'd never lie to us
梅宝姑娘
Mabel, girl
因为你真心爱我们
We know you love us so
这就是我为什么得放你们走了
And that's why I've got to let you go.
-当我思念你  -呃
- When I think about you - Uh...
这里面真有信息  我发誓
There's a message in there, I swear!
我们还是把窗户关了吧
Let me just close the window.
等等  等一下  快听
Wait! Wait! Here.
你现在在我的控制之下
You are now under my control
你的思想是我的
Your mind is mine
罗比  我们的歌里怎么会有这个
Robbie, what's that doing in our song?
宝贝  我保证  我一点也不知道这些信息的事
Baby, I promise. I don't know anything about those messages.
事实上  那首歌根本不是我写的
In fact, I didn't even write that song.
是我从别的乐队拿来的
I ripped it off some other band.
那么我们没事了  对吧
So we're all good, right?
不  我们一点也不好
No! We're not all good.
我根本不在乎这些信息
I don't care about the messages.
你说这是你写给我的歌
You said you wrote that song for me,
而且我还以为这很温馨呢  你个大骗子
And I actually thought it was sweet, you big liar!
我知道  我懂  我的确说了很多谎话
I know, I know, I lie about a lot of stuff.
偷用你的化妆品啦  和熊搏斗啦  但即使
Like using your makeup and fighting a bear. Although--
别说了  你知道吗  我们结束了  罗比  我们完了
No. You know what? It's over, Robbie. We're through.
什么  温蒂
What?! Wendy!
再见
Good-bye.
哈哈  我们赢了
Ha ha! We won!
孩子  这胜利属于每一个手太软或太胖
Kid, this is a victory for every guy whose hands
以至于不能演奏乐器的人
are too weak or fat to play a musical instrument.
没有你我是不可能做到的  斯坦叔公
I couldn't have done it without you, Grunkle Stan.
嘿  既然你今晚也没别的事了
Um, hey! Now that your night is free,
我和斯坦叔公想着去玩保龄球什么的  你看怎么样呢
Me and Grunkle Stan were thinkin' maybe bowling or something?
你是说真的吗  现在去
Are you serious? Right now?
啊  男人们都是怎么了
Uhh! What is wrong with guys?!
你们都只想着自己
You only think about yourselves!
你们让我一个人静一静
All of you should just leave me alone!
-哦  天哪  -如果这能让你好过一点的话
- Ohh, man. - Look, if it makes you feel any better,
世界末日要来了
The apocalypse is coming soon.
把你的黄金埋起来  你买了黄金的  对吧
Bury your gold. You've been buying gold, right?
我们得拯救男孩们
We've gotta save the boys.
我已经准备好保卫自己了
I'm prepared to defend myself.
嗨  大伙儿  真不好意思  我刚才发神经了
Hi, guys. I'm sorry I went bonkers.
一首上口的歌让我意识到你们是对的
A catchy song made me realize that you were right.
你们会原谅我吗
Can you ever forgive me?
当然
Of course!
友谊修复
Friendship repaired.
发生什么了  梅宝姑娘
What's goin' on, Mabel girl?
你说你要给我们看什么
You said you had something you wanted to show us or some deal?
对啊  这个
Yep, this!
哟  老兄
Yo, dawg,
这个又大又圆又亮的傻瓜是谁
Who is this big, round, bright fool?!
查比・齐  那个是太阳
That, Chubby Z, is the sun!
这个笨蛋把我的眼睛灼烧疼了
That fool's making my eyes burn straight painful!
我要盯着它  把它盯下去
I'm gonna stare that fool down.
等等  这一大片绿茵茵的是什么啊
Yo, yo, hold up. What this big green mess?
那是大自然  深度・克里斯
That's nature, Deep Chris.
布拉茨曼再也不会来打搅你们了
Bratzman won't bother you anymore.
你们可以做自己想做的事
You can do anything you want to do,
去你们想去的地方  你们自由了
Go anywhere you want to go. You're free!
自由
Fuh-ree?
是啊  你们自由了
Free! You're free!
这意味着你们可以走了
It means you can skedaddle!
快走啊  走啊
Now, go! Go!
在我改变主意之前赶快离开这儿
Get out of here before I change my mind!
再见  姑娘
Good-bye, girl
他们熬不过一个星期的
They won't last a week.
女人啊  她们真是难解的迷  迪普
Women! They're the real mystery, Dip!
你毁了你的约会
You ruin your date,
把她的嬉皮士男朋友的车扔进大峡谷
drop their hippie boyfriend's van into a ravine,
但莫名其妙的是  你却变成了坏人
And somehow you're the bad guy.
不  这是我的错
No, it's my fault.
我不应该掺和到温蒂的个人生活中
I shouldn't have meddled in Wendy's personal life.
她现在肯定恨死我了
She probably hates me now.
别灰心  孩子  你的本意是好的
Ah, chin up, kid. You were trying to do the right thing.
即使你毁了她的感情  还损伤了我的车
Even though you destroyed her relationship and part of my car.
你觉得她会原谅我吗
You think she'll ever forgive me?
我打赌她会的
I bet she will.
在那之前  你仍然可以和我一起玩保龄球
And until then, you can always go bowling with me.
谢了  斯坦叔公
Thanks, Grunkle Stan.
别客气  孩子
Don't mention it, kid.
等等  是有什么东西在翻我们的垃圾桶吗
Wait a second. Is something rooting through our trash?
快滚开
Get outta here!
可恶的帅小伙
Darn beautiful men!
总来吃我的垃圾
Always eating out of my trash.
等下  什么
Wait. What?
姑娘  你让我行为如此疯狂
Girl, you got me acting so cray cray
疯狂  疯狂
cray cray
你说你不会做我的宝贝
You tell me that you won't be my baby
我们并不危险  姑娘
We're non-threatening, girl. Yeah.
见鬼  姑娘
Dang, girl.
2013.